vectorfree.com 2018-06-04

# Vector Free - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

**Vector Free's Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information by Vector Free, located at www.VectorFree.com.**

Vector Free has implemented all reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of personal information that we control. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Vector Free and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its third parties.

We collect personal information when you provide it to us by becoming a Vector Free member, when you sign up to receive our newsletters, participate in forum discussions, send us messages or emails or when you download or buy one of our products. By using or accessing Vector Free, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

When you become a Vector Free member, you create your own profile, which contains certain personal information, such as your name, nickname, your gender, your address, your email address and any other information that you provide to us. Your member information, as well as your (nick)name, email and avatar, are displayed to other people visiting the Vector Free website.

Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, marketplace listings or other items, this information may become publicly available.

Vector Free site usage information is occasionally collected automatically about your activities while visiting the Vector Free site, including what pages you view and when you view them and information about the browser you are using.

You agree and understand that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of passwords associated with any account you use to access the Vector Free website and services. Accordingly, you agree that you will be solely responsible for all activities that occur under your Vector Free account. If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password or of your account, you agree to notify Vector Free immediately at “info at VectorFree dot com”.

 **USE OF INFORMATION**  
Profile information you submit to Vector Free will be available to visitors of the website and limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. Vector Free may send you website-related announcements from time to time. Generally, you may opt out of such emails by unsubscribing to our email updates.

Vector Free may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) permitted by you 2) reasonably necessary to offer the service or 3) legally requested as we might be required to disclose user information in compliance with applicable laws.

We may use third parties to facilitate our operations, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these activities.

Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Vector Free specified purposes.

We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers. We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other websites, brands or companies.

 **USE OF FACEBOOK SOCIAL PLUGIN**  
Vector Free uses social plugins provided by the social network Facebook. The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo or the notice “Facebook Social Plugin”. When you visit a page of Vector Free that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Facebook to receive information about you having accessed the respective page of the Vector Free website.

If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking “Like”, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Facebook and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Facebook, there is possibility that the plugins transmits your IP-address to Facebook. Vector Free has no influence on the data gathered by the social plugin.

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Facebook, please log off Facebook before entering our website. You can block Facebook social plugins by using add-ons for your browser.

For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Facebook, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Facebook’s privacy policy: [fb.com/policy.php](http://fb.com/policy.php).

 **USE OF GOOGLE+ PLUGIN**  
Vector Free uses the social plugin provided by Google’s social network site plus.google.com. The Google plugin is labeled with the Google +1 logo. If you are logged into Google, your visit can be assigned to your Google account. When you visit pages of Vector Free that contain the plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Google servers. Google directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the information into the website, enabling Google to receive data about you having accessed the page.

If you interact with the Google+ plugin, for example by clicking the “+1” button, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Google and stored by it. If you do not want Google to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Google, please log off Google before entering our website.

For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Google, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Google’s privacy policy: [google.com/intl/en/privacy/](http://google.com/intl/en/privacy/)

 **USE OF TWITTER PLUGIN**  
Vector Free contains a social plugin from online social networking site Twitter. When you visit a page of our website that contains the Twitter plugin your browser establishes a direct connection to the servers of Twitter.com, which is used to retrieve the data generated by the plugin. Through this process, Twitter is aware that you have visited this website. If you are logged in to Twitter while browsing Vector Free, Twitter can match your visit with your account. By interacting with the plugin, this information is sent directly to Twitter and processed there. If you would like to opt out, please log out of Twitter before visiting Vector Free. For more information about Twitter’s privacy policy, visit [Twitter.com/privacy](http://twitter.com/privacy).

 **THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**  
Advertisements that appear on Vector Free are sometimes served directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked.

Vector Free does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Vector Free unless you choose to share it with them.

 **SECURITY**  
Vector Free takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as Paypal password or credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

 **CHANGING OR REMOVING INFORMATION**  
Access and control over most personal information on Vector Free is readily available through the profile editing tools. Vector Free users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Vector Free account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available.

 **UNDER AGE 13 POLICY**  
Vector Free does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to become a member. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Vector Free. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Vector Free or send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

 **BETWEEN AGES 13-18 POLICY**  
Vector Free recommends that minors 13-18 years old ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet

 **LINKS**  
Vector Free may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 15, 2011. We may revise these policies at any time. Questions? Please direct questions regarding this Privacy Policy to “info at VectorFree dot com”.
